

ROMJAN

- Dubai United Arab Emirates
- +971527807057

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://romjan123.github.io/romjan/
- https://twitter.com/romjan1995
- https://linkedin.com/in/romjan1995

Professional Summary

Organized **Waiter** with experience in **more than 2 years** restaurant environments. Effective creator of service structures with thoughtful organization. Efficient house manager and facilitator of rapid table turnover, boosting volume and increasing sales opportunities.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Data Entry
- First Aid/CPR
- Attention to Detail
- MS Office

- Problem-Solving
- Excellent Communication
- Food and Beverage Service
- Alcohol Ordering
- Restaurant Operation
- Team Player

Work History

03.2022 - 02.2023

Restaurant Waiter

Green Valley Event Management - Dubai, AE

- Replenished food items, paper products and canned goods to keep pantry well-stocked during busy periods.
- Worked with POS system to place orders, manage bills and handle complimentary items.
- Checked identification for minimum age for sale of alcoholic beverages.
- Noted special patron requests and followed up with kitchen to confirm delivery.
- Shared knowledge of menu items and flavors, enabling customers to make personal decisions based on taste and interest.
- Displayed enthusiasm and promoted excellent service to customers, successfully increasing referrals and walk-in business.
- Maintained customer satisfaction with timely table check-ins to assess food and beverage needs

02.2021 - 02.2022

Restaurant Waiter

Alabar Enterprise - Dubai, AE

- Arranged and prepared tables for customers to offer memorable experiences to guests and foster repeat business.
- Quickly reset and cleaned up tables after customers left to enable

- speedy turnaround and guest flow.
- Cultivated warm relationships with regular customers.
- Replenished food items, paper products and canned goods to keep pantry well-stocked during busy periods.
- Explained menu items and suggested appropriate options for food alleray concerns.
- Bussed and reset tables to keep dining room and work areas clean.
- Used slow periods to restock supplies, ice, trays and delivery bags.
- Increased sales significantly by upselling higher-end products to customers.

07.2017 - 07.2019

Food Server

HB-Brand - Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

- Established strong vendor relationships to maintain and support business.
- Organized and replenished supplies at food stations to optimize team performance.
- Completed table resets by wiping down surfaces and refilling condiments.
- Greeted incoming guests and managed accurate seating based on customer desires and server loads.
- Cultivated warm relationships with regular customers.
- Explained menu items and suggested appropriate options for food allergy concerns.
- Elevated customer satisfaction through followup and enthusiastic customer service.
- Added food items, beverages and utensils to trays and immediately delivered to correct rooms

Education

07.2019

Under Graduate, Accounting, National University of Bangladesh - Dhaka

- Continuing education in Accounting
- Compete BBA 2nd Semester out of 4 semester in 2019

07.2015

High School Diploma, Purbo Madaripur College - Dhaka

Languages

English

Hindi

Upper intermediate (B2)

Advanced (C1)

Arabic

Elementary (A2)